fantastigames.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy - FantastiGames

Last modified June 1, 2012

FantastiGames.com ("FantastiGames") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about FantastiGames Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how FantastiGames receives, collects and uses information in connection with its Site located at [www.FantastiGames.com](http://www.fantastigames.com/) (“Site”).

Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, capitalized terms shall have the same meaning ascribed to them in the Terms of Use.

**Collection and Use of Information**

**Information You Provide:**

You can use the Site and access the Software and Service without providing any Personal Information (as defined below). However, in connection with other activities through the Site, you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information, which may include your name, email address, age, gender, address, telephone number(s), and any other self-identifying information (all "Personal Information"). **It is entirely optional for you to engage in these activities.** FantastiGames collects this Personal Information primarily for the following purposes: (i) personalized experience of the Service; (ii) to manage and maintain users' personal preferences; (iii) to email you with news, updates and offers, and (iv) respond to communications from you. 

**Information We Automatically Collect:**

FantastiGames does not automatically collect any Personal Information on or through the Site or Service, except as may be provided by you in connection with your voluntary communications described above. However, when you use the Site, FantastiGames may also automatically collect certain information about your computer to facilitate, evaluate and verify your use of the Site. For example, FantastiGames may use “cookies,” “web beacons” and similar devices to track your activities on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. A web-beacon is a small transparent gif image that is embedded in an HTML page or email used to track when the page or email has been viewed. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are on the Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. FantastiGames' use of cookies or similar devices is not linked to any Personal Information. 

When you visit the Site, FantastiGames may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that you visit. FantastiGames collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. FantastiGames will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with the aggregate data of its users. Please be aware that some non-personally identifiable information such as Uniform Resource Locators (“URL’s) or Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses could become Personal Information when combined by third parties with the ISP’s records. **FantastiGames does NOT do this with your information.**

**By accepting these Terms and Privacy Policy you are affirmatively consenting to the use of cookies as described herein.**

**You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. However, the Service may not function properly if you disable cookies.**

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

FantastiGames does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties without your permission or as provided below. FantastiGames may disclose your information if FantastiGames believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on FantastiGames; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of FantastiGames (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of FantastiGames services or members of the public. FantastiGames may share aggregated non-personally identifiable demographic information about users with third party advertising and content companies. This information does not identify individual users and FantastiGames does not link aggregate user data with Personal Information. 

FantastiGames may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help it provide, analyze and improve the Site, Software and Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, information processing and improvement of the Site’s features and services. These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on behalf of FantastiGames and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy. 

**Third party advertisers and websites**

FantastiGames does not actively share Personal Information with third party advertisers for their direct marketing purposes unless you give FantastiGames your consent or as described below. Advertisers, however, may obtain public information about you from your user profile and other public sources. Remember, third parties will have access to your Personal Information if you provide it to them. For example, if you want to buy offers, goods or services from through third party advertisers on the Site, the transaction may be facilitated on the third party’s website. You will then have to provide the third party with the information required (such as for example name, shipping address, credit card info etc), which will them be subject to their specific privacy policies. If you access another website or promotion and/or service through a website operated by any entity other than FantastiGames, that site is referred to as a “Third Party Site”. Unless FantastiGames clearly indicates otherwise at the time of collection, FantastiGames does not share Personal Information with Third Party Sites. Please be aware however that these Third Party Sites may collect information about you. Please see the Third Party Site’s privacy policy to better understand what information is collected, how it is used and shared, and your choices regarding control. FantastiGames has no control over these linked Third Party Sites, each of which has a separate privacy and data collection practice, independent of this Privacy Policy. FantastiGames does not monitor, control, or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any Third Party Site. As such, FantastiGames is not responsible for, or have control over, the content or the privacy policies of these Third Party Sites. **You must read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit when linking from the Site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by FantastiGames.**

In addition, please be aware that since the Service is free and “ad-supported,” some of our affiliates and partners (“Service Partners”) may request that you download and install certain advertising enabling Software (e.g., “Admuse” provided by our Service Provider Excent Technologies, Ltd.) or other similar advertising software (“Ad Software”). This Ad Software enables and supports the appearance of advertisements integrated within certain Applications you may use on the Service. After you install the Ad Software, advertisements will appear while you use the Service according to predefined viewing requirements and frequency caps. From time to time, this Ad Software may connect to external servers in order to report performance records such as the advertisements that were displayed, the impressions received, and which, if any, were clicked on. But please note, the Ad Software does not report any personally identifiable information. 

By installing the Ad Software from a Service Provider you are affirmatively accepting the right of these third parties to (i) display advertisements on the Service, at their sole and absolute discretion without having to receive your further authorization and without any compensation to you; (ii) determine the timing, frequency, placement and Excent of advertising by each of the Service Providers, at its sole discretion and (iii) place or recognize a unique "cookie(s)" on your computer and, in some cases, collect data through the use of cookies as further described in the Service Provider’s Privacy Policy which you should review and accept. **You should review Excent Technologies, Ltd. Privacy Notice[here](http://www.freeridegames.com/do/general?partner=Default&jspName=privacy) which describes how Excent receives, collects and uses you information.**

When you download Ad Software, such as Admuse, You agree and acknowledge that the Software may target Ads based on non-personally identifiable information (e.g., geographical location). You agree that the Software will collect the non-personally identifiable information items, including for research, royalty and targeting purposes. 

You should be aware that some jurisdictions prohibit the downloading of “adware”. By downloading or installing the client side of the Software containing Admuse, for example, you declare and represent that your computer is not located in such a jurisdiction (e.g. the State of Alaska, U.S.) 

**This Privacy Policy applies solely to information about you collected by FantastiGames and not our Service Providers or other third parties.**

**Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). FantastiGames never knowingly collects or maintains information at or on our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of the Site is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, please contact us at privacy@FantastiGames.com. 

**Security**

FantastiGames takes reasonable precaution to protect your information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although FantastiGames cannot guarantee that your information will not be subject to unauthorized access, FantastiGames has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the your information. Your information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. 

If you contact FantastiGames by e-mail or a “contact us” or similar feature on the Site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. 

In the unlikely event that FantastiGames believes that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, FantastiGames may seek to notify you of that development if you have provided FantastiGames with your email address or other method of communicating with you. If a notification is appropriate, FantastiGames will endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances. 

IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE SITE FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE THAT DIFFER FROM UNITED STATES LAWS, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICES, WHICH ARE GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW, THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND FANTASTIGAMES’ TERMS OF USE, YOU ARE TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES AND YOU CONSENT TO THAT TRANSFER. ADDITIONALLY, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO AND PROCESSED IN COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN IN YOUR COUNTRY. 

**Data Retention**

FantastiGames will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services and fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy. FantastiGames may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with its legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, FantastiGames will try to delete your information quickly and upon request. 

**Business Transitions**

In the event that FantastiGames goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. FantastiGames will post a notice on this Site of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information FantastiGames may have prior to such transfer. 

**Changes to Policy**

From time to time, FantastiGames may revise this Policy. FantastiGames will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information FantastiGames collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. If FantastiGames makes a change in its data collection policy that would result in a materially more permissive use of your Personal Information, FantastiGames will obtain your prior affirmative consent before implementing the change with respect to your data if we have your contact information or we will provide more prominent notice. You should also visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Notice. 

**Change or Removal of Information**

If you have provided FantastiGames with Personal Information, you can review, update, correct, edit or delete your Personal Information at any time by contacting us at info@FantastiGames.com. 

**Contact Information**

If you believe FantastiGames is not adhering to this Privacy Policy or you have any questions in connection with this Privacy Policy, please contact FantastiGames at: privacy@FantastiGames.com or by writing to FantastiGames.com., Attention: FantastiGames Privacy Policy Administrator. 

Koyote-Lab Inc.  
40 kimonos St.  
3095 Limassol  
Cyprus.
